Did the Young Master actually
get it done?
What?
You're ignoring me
just because I couldn't
get Mrs. He's nudes?
You can't even handle such a simple task,
Young Master?
Are you mocking me?
Come find me
when you actually get her nudes.
When have I ever broken my word?
There are plenty.
Why should I listen to you?
You probably don't know this,
Young Master.
I've compiled the documents
proving your infertility.
If anything happens to me,
the media will be the first to know.
Fine.
You've got guts.
Li Zhangxin,
how dare you use He Shi to set me up.
Spare her for now.
Let's see what tricks she can play.
We'll settle all the scores then.
This is you.
This is an old photo of me.
Keep it as a reward.
So beautiful.
Today is not a good time.
I'll go back first.
You give me the cold shoulder
as soon as the master returns.
Roujing,
has He Shi been acting strange lately?
No.
Thank you for your concern.
It's really hard being a woman.
Look at you.
You're heavily pregnant now
and can't satisfy He Shi
in many ways.
He's bound to fool around,
right?
You know
I can't control He Shi.
But he shouldn't cheat
with someone close to us.
As the mistress of the He Manor,
I absolutely won't allow this to happen.
Someone close...
Come here.
Slow
down.
Li Zhangxin!
Impossible.
Zhangxin isn't that kind of person.
Silly,
you never truly know a person.
I'm just worried you'll get fooled.
I don't have solid proof yet,
so I need you to keep an eye on them.
He Shi might have intentions for Zhangxin,
but she would never do that.
Haven't you heard that even the toughest
woman can't resist a persistent man?
Besides,
He Shi is
several social classes above Li Zhangxin.
What normal woman
could resist that kind of temptation?
I think you know that better than anyone,
right?
I'm sure I locked the door.
How did you get in?
I have the keys to all the rooms
in this manor.
Including Zhang Xin's room?
I've got the photos.
Is it time to keep your promise?
You can't call these nude photos.
They only count as artistic photos.
Besides,
these photos
were taken when Zhang Xin was young.
You didn't take them.
Anyway, I've got the photos.
You didn't say they had to be fresh.
I know you're interested in me.
He Shi's status
is several classes above Li Zhangxin's.
What normal woman
could resist such temptation?
Let go of me.
Zhangxin.
Honey,
you're here too.
I was just planning to chat with Zhangxin.
Thank you.
Roujing,
what do you need? I'll help you.
Mrs. He asked me
to find the foot bath bag.
She said it's on the cabinet.
Come down quickly, I'll get it for you.
Roujing,
are you okay?
Why is there oil on the floor?
How dare you, Li Zhangxin!
You actually framed
the First Young Mistress!
No wonder Zhang Xin
asked me to clean the room.
It was a scheme all along.
What exactly happened?
Master,
your eldest grandson is gone.
What?
The culprit is her,
Li Zhangxin.
Master He,
I really didn't push
the First Young Mistress.
I was trying to help her fetch something.
But the floor was too slippery,
causing her to fall.
Stop making excuses.
I have a witness.
Roujing,
you tell us.
Did Li Zhangxin really push you?